You've been traveling alone
and must be exhausted.
Today,
with the rustic charm
and beautiful scenery of the mountains,
why don't you
spend it with me?
Unbelievable.
I dressed up like this and still couldn't win you over.
Just you wait.
How can you sleep so soundly?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Master.
It seems
another extraordinary person
has arrived in the city.
Want to buy a talisman?
Good luck charms.
Wealth pouches.
Peace amulets.
Things to pray for peace,
we have it all.
No, thanks. I already have one.
Thank you.
Want to buy a talisman?
No, thanks.
I really don't need it.
I have one.
Want to buy a talisman?
Good luck charms.
Wealth pouches.
Peace amulets.
No, thanks.
Things to pray for peace,
we have it all.
Want to buy a talisman?
Good luck charms.
Wealth pouches.
Want to buy a talisman?
Good luck charms.
Wealth pouches.
Peace amulets.
Master.
What are we doing here?
Let's stay here first.
Stay here?
It will cost a lot of silver.
Don't you have silver?
This silver is to be handed over to the government.
Handing it over
is official business.
Since it's official business,
we must do things by the book.
We can't just sleep on the streets.
Are you two
staying
or bathing?
We'll stay
and bathe.
You really have a good eye.
Ercheng
is famous for its hot springs.
And Miaoren Bathhouse
is the best in Ercheng.
Coming here,
you'll definitely be satisfied.
Then
we'll book two deluxe rooms.
One deluxe room is enough.
I spoke too much.
Please go upstairs.
Xiao Wang.
Coming.
Please go upstairs, you two.
Miss,
do you want to stay
or enjoy the hot spring?
Master.
Since it's on public expense,
why don't we get two rooms?
There's only one bed.
We should spend what we need to spend,
and save what
we can save.
So everything goes by your rules.
What are you saying?
Nothing.
You sleep on the bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
The hot spring here
seems to be famous.
You are tired from the journey.
Why not take a dip in the hot spring?
It can relieve your fatigue.
Okay.
I haven't been in a hot spring before.
Master,
aren't you going?
I want to be alone for a while.
After you finish with the hot spring,
remember to ask for a set of bedding.
Okay.
Still shy.
Master.
Those three checked into Miaoren Hot Spring.
One of them
is taking a bath.
The other two
are resting in their own rooms.
The three of them are all separated.
Seems they don't have much capability.
Go.
Go meet them.
If they are obedient,
keep them penned up.
If they are not,
just feed them to the little ones.
So comfortable.
Why not enjoy it since we paid for it?
This master is indeed different from us mortals.
Truly different.
It feels so good.
Not bad.
Young master.
Don't be afraid, young master.
It's me.
Madam.
We paid silver to bathe in this hot spring.
You must be joking, young master.
I just came to ask
if you are satisfied
with our hot spring.
The hot spring?
It's excellent.
Excellent.
Please enjoy, young master.
Is this
free?
You are really joking, young master.
This is complimentary from the shop.
There's more if it's not enough.
I'll give you
as much as you want.
Then I won't be polite.
Eat slowly, young master.
Are there any more grapes?
Bring some more.
Okay.
Once you finish eating,
I will go get them.
Where are you from?
What are you doing in Er City?
We're looking for the local authorities.
Why are you looking for them?
Looking for the authorities...
My master
told me not to speak carelessly.
Master?
What master?
The master staying upstairs.
He's an amazing demon hunter.
Sorry.
It's okay.
The master you just mentioned,
is he Taoist
or Buddhist?
Well,
I don't know either.
Anyway, he's just really powerful.
Then you must be very powerful too.
Me?
I'm not very powerful yet.
But
I want to become his disciple.
Given time,
I will definitely become very powerful too.
So,
he is just an easy target.
Let's kill him first,
then deal with those two.
Ping Jieqiang Hai Hui.